Guide to the Knight Biggerstaff papers, 1923-2000,
Biggerstaff, Knight papers, 1923-2000
- Series XXIV. 1972-1978, Post-retirement correspondence
  - Laffey, Ella 1962-1984 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Laffey, John 1966-1985 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Laffey, John 1966-1985 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Leonard, Jane Kate 1964-1985 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Leonard, Jane Kate 1974-1983 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Leonard, Jane Kate (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Leonard, Jane Kate (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Mikelich, Mira (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Murray, Dian 1974-1985 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Nagazumi, Akira 1963-1971 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Glenik, John 1965-1983 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Glenik, John (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Rawski, Tom (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Pope, Harold 1966-1973 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Reber, Lindsey 1966 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Ricklefs, Merle 1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Rokjer, Thomas 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Shiqetani, Marianne Donovan (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Surette, Gerald 1963-1967 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Tyrner-Stastny, Alice 1968-1976 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Trocki, Carl 1968-1976 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Ts'as, Ignatius 1966-1971 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Ungar, Esta 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Wilson, Constance 1963-1969 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Wyatt, David 1962-1969 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Recommendatons A-D (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Recommendations E-G (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Recommendations H-K (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Recommendations L-P (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Recommendations R-J (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Recommendations T-Z (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Term Reports (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Misc (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Tsong-wuen Lin Paper 1969 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Cnner, Alison Paper 1968 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - James Plunkett Paper 1972 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Paper: Ben Bastspm 1971 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Hist 205 Reading Assignments, Lecture Notes (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Thesis - John Kremers Whitmore 1968 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Paper - Donald Holock 1969 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Paper - William Dockey (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Paper - Richard Caulton 1967 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Paper - J Kenneth Olenik 1968 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Hist 593 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Hist 394 Spring 1977 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Hist 394 Spring 1972 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Hist 394 Spring Spring 1973 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Hist 394 Spring 1974 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Hist 257 Fall 1972 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - ? (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - American Historical Association 87th Meeting 1972 (Box 28)
  - American Historical Association 88th Meeting 1973 (Box 28)
  - Association for Asian Studies, Inc. 38th Meeting 1986 (Box 28)
  - Association for Asian Studies, Inc. 39th Meeting 1987 (Box 28)
  - Association for Asian Studies, Inc. 38th Meeting 1986 (Box 28)
  - American Historical Association Supplement 1970 (Box 28)
  - Reference Works for Modern Chinese History (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - 593 Taiping Rebellion and Its Consequences (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - 593 T'ung-chin Restoration and Its Cause (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - 593 Western Impact and Chinese Response to 1898 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - 593 1900-1912 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - 593 New Culture and May 4 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - 593 1920's Revolution (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - 593 Education, Art, Lit, etc. 1930's (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - 593 Pre-War-Kuomintang (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - 593 Pre-War - Communists (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - 593 War Years (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - 593 1945 - 1949 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - 593 Questions (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - 593-4 Questionnaire: Chinese History Program (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - 394 Questionnaire (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Grad Students 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - New Paultz MA program 1969-1971 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Books for Modern Chinese History (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - News Articales (photcopies) (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Yinmaw Kau Doctoral Thesis I 1968 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Yinmaw Kau II 1968 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Yinmaw Kau III 1968 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Department of History (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - NEH Applications (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Chen, Theo H.C. 1972 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Personal 1945-1949 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Richard C. Howard - survey 1963 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Shanghai Polytechnic etc. (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Shanghai Polytechnic etc. (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Chinese Newspaper Clippings (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - China 1949-1950 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Paper - Ella Laffey (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Paper - Thomas Rawski (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Notes On Far Eastern Studies in America No.12 1943 (Box 29)
  - Notes On Far Eastern Studies in America No.11 1942 (Box 29)
  - Notes On Far Eastern Studies in America No.10 1942 (Box 29)
  - Notes On Far Eastern Studies in America No.9 1941 (Box 29)
  - Notes On Far Eastern Studies in America No.8 1941 (Box 29)
  - Notes On Far Eastern Studies in America No.7 1940 (Box 29)
  - Notes On Far Eastern Studies in America No.6 1940 (Box 29)
  - Notes On Far Eastern Studies in America No.5 1939 (Box 29)
  - Notes On Far Eastern Studies in America No.4 1939 (Box 29)
  - Notes On Far Eastern Studies in America No.3 1938 (Box 29)
  - Notes On Far Eastern Studies in America No.2 1938 (Box 29)
  - Notes On Far Eastern Studies in America No.1 1937 (Box 29)
  - Notes On Far Eastern Studies in America 1937 (Box 29)
  - Harvard Law School: Studies in Chinese Law No.17 1971 (Box 29)
  - Harvard Law School: Studies in Chinese Law No.16 1971 (Box 29)
  - Harvard Law School: Studies in Chinese Law No.15 1971 (Box 29)
  - Harvard Law School: Studies in Chinese Law No.13 1970 (Box 29)
  - Harvard Law School: Studies in Chinese Law No.3 1966 (Box 29)
  - Harvard Journal of Asiatic Studies 1941 (Box 29)
  - Bijdragen 1969 (Box 29)
  - Bijdragen 1971 (Box 29)
  - A consideration of three versions of the Babad tanah Djawi, with excerpts on the fall of the Madjapahit 1969 (Box 29)
  - Progress of Chinese Studies in the United States of America No.1 1931 (Box 29)
  - American Council of Learned Societies No.10 1929 (Box 29)
  - Books on the Orient Asia and Africa 1972 (Box 29)
  - Historians and American Far Eastern Policy 1966 (Box 29)
  - SCAN: Student Course Analysis 1972 (Box 29)
  - Quotations from Chairman Mao Tse-Tung 1967 (Box 29)
  - Themes from Hist. Chairman 1972-1977 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Memos from Hist. Chairman 1964-1971 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Book Reviews 1956-1979 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Biggerstaff relat. with Univ. 1956-1976 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Dockery, William 1973-1975 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Herman, Alice 1973-1981 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Herman, Alice (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - David Porter 1973 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Ron Taylor (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - McCullough, Marilyn 1967-1973 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Morse, Lawrence 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Proposed to Hist. Chairman (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Beckham, Joan 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Oriental History Course 1970-1971 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Job Inquiries 1967-1972 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Peterson Correspondence 1972-1975 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Hist 191 [206] 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Latest Hist. 394 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Hist 394 Spring 1977 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - My Replacement 1971-1973 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Cochran, Sherman 1977-1983 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Sherm's Students (Cochran) 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Maps: China, Manchuria (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Rubbing (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - The Grand Council in the Ch'ing Dynasty (Box 30)
  - Magic and Science in Western Yunnan 1943 (Box 30)
  - A Critique of American Bourgeois Historiography on China: Problems of Social Development in the Nineteenth and Early Twentieth Century 1968 (Box 30)
  - Harvard Journal of Asiatic Studies - Volume 30 1970 (Box 30)
  - Modern Chinese History Project No.36 1970 (Box 30)
  - National Central Library Bulletin 1970 (Box 30)
  - Handicraft and Manufactured Cotton Textiles in China 1970 (Box 30)
  - December 9, 1935: Student Nationalism and the China Christian Colleges 1967 (Box 30)
  - On the Possibility of an Autonomous History of Modern Southeast Asia 1961 (Box 30)
  - The Wu-Shih-Shan Incident of 1878 1964 (Box 30)
  - Gods, Ghosts, and Ancestors: Social Correlates of the Supernatural, A Case Study of Chinese Religion 1966 (Box 30)
  - What the Study of China Can Do for Social Science 1964 (Box 30)
  - Modern Chinese History Project No. 19 1964 (Box 30)
  - The Concept of Parliamentary Government in 19th Century China 1963 (Box 30)
  - The Humanistic Tradition in The Century Ahead 1966 (Box 30)
  - Philosophy, East and West 1953 (Box 30)
  - Modern Chinese History Project No. 26 1965 (Box 30)
  - Childhood Association, Sexual Attraction, and the Incest Taboo: A Chinese Case 1966 (Box 30)
  - Acheh in the Seventeenth Century Asian Trade. (Box 30)
  - Chiang Kai-shek's Waterloo: The Battle of the Hwai-Hai 1956 (Box 30)
  - Modern Chinese History Project No. 17 1964 (Box 30)
  - China's History in Marxian 1961 (Box 30)
  - Modern Chinese History Project No. 10 1962 (Box 30)
  - Bibliography of Dr. Hu Shih's Writings in Western Languages 1963 (Box 30)
  - Dr. Sun Yat-Sen and Chinese Secret Societies 1963 (Box 30)
  - The Kiangsi Soviet Period: A Bibliographical Review on the Ch'en Ch'eng Collection 1970 (Box 30)
  - Studies in Soviet Thought 1970 (Box 30)
  - "Religions and the Development Process in Asia" 1970 (Box 30)
  - The Nature of Provincial Political Authority in Late Ch'ing Times: Chang Chih-tung in Canton 1970 (Box 30)
  - An Interpretation of Chinese Social Structure and Its Changes 1946 (Box 30)
  - McCarthyism and Our Asia Policy 1969 (Box 30)
  - "Industrial Enterprise in Twentieth-Century China: The Chee Hsin Cement Co." 1967 (Box 30)
  - Siam and Laos 1963 (Box 30)
  - Nineteenth-Century China: The Disintegration of the Old Order and the Impact of the West 1968 (Box 30)
  - Symposium on Chinese Studies 1968 (Box 30)
  - Sun Yat-Sen and Chinese History 1968 (Box 30)
  - Journal of Asian and African Studies 1967 (Box 30)
  - Li Hung-Chang and the Kiangnan Shipbuilding Program 1970 (Box 30)
  - Verfassung Und Recht in Ubersee 1972 (Box 30)
  - La Formation D'un Rebelle: Liu Yongfun et la Creation de L'armee des Pavillon Noirs 1970 (Box 30)
  - Historical Interaction of China and Vietnam: Institutional and Cultural Themes 1969 (Box 30)
  - Chinese Overlordship and Western Penetration in Maritime Asia: A Late Ch'ing Reappraisal of Chinese Maritime Relations 1972 (Box 30)
  - Bulletin No. 29 1972 (Box 30)
  - Peita as a Revolutionary Environment: The Twenties and the Sixties 1970 (Box 30)
  - Introduction to the Economy of China 1970 (Box 30)
  - Revue D'histoire Moderne et Contemporaine 1969 (Box 30)
  - A Chinese Official's Experiences During the First Opium War 1933 (Box 30)
  - Pacific Affairs Bibliographies No. 1: The Personal Chronicale of the First Manchu Emeperor 1936 (Box 30)
  - Sinological Research Work in Free China During the War Period (Box 30)
  - The T'ai Miao of Peking (Box 30)
  - The Last of the Immortals (Box 30)
  - Far Eastern Culture and Society (Box 30)
  - T'oung Pao Archives 1938 (Box 30)
  - Chinese Education During the War (Box 30)
  - As China's Friend "Mei-Kuo" First (Box 30)
  - The Ting Hsien Experiment (Box 30)
  - Knight and Camilla Correspondence 1949 (Box 30)
  - Tell The People - Mass Education in China (Box 30)
  - The Local Government of China (Box 30)
  - Lusin: A Chronolgical Record 1939 (Box 30)
  - Harvard Journal of Asiatic Studies 1943 (Box 30)
  - The Language Students of the East India Company's Canton Factory (Box 30)
  - A Study in Miniature of Chinese Population 1951 (Box 30)
  - The Senior Returned Students, A Brief Account of the Chinese Educational Commission 1932 (Box 30)
  - Diplomatic Audiences at the Court of China (Box 30)
  - Occasional Papers (Box 30)
  - The "False Edict" of 1849 1961 (Box 30)
  - President's Valedictory Address 1866 (Box 30)
  - Tirage A Part Du T'oung Pao (Box 30)
  - La Haute Asie 1931 (Box 30)
  - Translation of the Text of the Resolutions Adopted at the Closing Session of the Political Consultative Council 1946 (Box 30)
  - Political Consultative Conference (Box 30)
  - Map of China (Box 30)
  - Map of Southeast Asia 1966 (Box 30)
  - Land Classification Map of Tompkins County, New York 1930 (Box 30)
  - The National Geographic Magazine: Mexico, Central America, and the West Indies 1939 (Box 30)
  - Fortune's Map of South America in Globular Perspective 1966 (Box 30)
  - National History and the Kuo Shih Kuan 1966 (Box 30)
  - card files 1700s-1949 (Box 31)
  - The Yenchinian 1929-1930 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - TWK (Tungwen College) calendars 1879-1898 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - "Yenching Faculty Families" newsletter 1985-1995 (Box 32, Folder 3-5)
  - Knight Biggerstaff graduate students 1968-1974 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Cornell East Asia Program newsletter, Fall 1992 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Directory of Japan Specialists and Japanese Studies Institutions in the United States and Canada survey form) 19-- (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Yenching Faculty Families 2000 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - 2 sauce dishes, 1 ashtray, 1 cup, 1 page holder, 1 Italian university medal 19-- (Box 33)
  - Photos 1930-1973 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Korea 19-- (Box 34)
  - Yun Kang, Korea 1935, 1941 (Box 34)
  - Japan 19-- (Box 34)
  - China and Japan 1929 1936 (Box 34)
  - Hangchow [Hangzhou], China 19-- (Box 34)
  - Miscellaneous China pictures 1928-1931 (Box 34)
  - Peking, China 1928 (Box 34)
  - Peking-Yenching, China 1928-1931 (Box 34)
  - Yenching, China 1931 (Box 34)
  - Pan Shan, China 19-- (Box 34)
  - Peitaiho, China 19-- (Box 34)
  - Summer trip 1929 (Box 34)
  - k[night]'s trip to Siam, Spring 1930 (Box 34)
  - Trip up Yangtze 1931 (Box 34)
  - Temple in Western Hills, Summer Palace, etc.(3 envelopes) 1928-1931 (Box 34)
  - Correspondence 1981-1998 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Janet Smith Rhodes letters 1996-1999 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Diaries, journals 1945-1975 (Box 35, Folder 3-6)
  - Family history in China: Ben Anderson's father 1998 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Family history in China: John Ferguson family 1975, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Chapter III, 1st draft 19-- (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Chapter 27, 1st draft 19-- (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Modern China and Japan chapters, Houghton Mifflin 1987 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Modern China and Japan chapters, Knopf 1987 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Houghton Mifflin "World" history 1979 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Bibliography 1904-1948 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Sherm's course 1982 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - History 394 1973-1977 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - History 191 1973 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - History 203 1971 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - High school course 1978 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Yenching College, Women's College of Peking University 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Beijing University 19-- (Box 35, Folder 18)